A Guide to the David Rockefeller papers, Associates, Warren T. Lindquist papers FA102
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1978 Accession, 1960-1977; 2
  - Business-Labor Working Group: Implementation, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 534)
  - Business Labor Working Group: Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 64, Folder 535)
  - Business Labor Working Group: Distribution Items, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 536)
  - Business-Labor Working Group: Ad Hoc Committee on Current Issues, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 537)
  - Business-Labor Working Group: New York Court of Appeals Opinion, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 538)
  - Business-Labor Working Group: Work Space and Candidates, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 539)
  - Business-Labor Working Group: Finance Working Group, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 540)
  - Business-Labor Working Group: Working Group Lists, 1976-1977 (Box 65, Folder 541)
  - Business-Labor Working Group: Manufacturing and Industrial Working Group, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 542)
  - Business-Labor Working Group: Port and International Trade Group, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 543-545)
  - Business-Labor Working Group: Business Services Working Group, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 546)
  - Business-Labor Working Group: Communications, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 547)
  - Business-Labor Working Group: Construction and Housing Working Group, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 548)
  - Business-Labor Working Group: Meeting Books, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 549-555)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank: Shortage of Capital, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 556)
  - Conservation, Rehabilitation, and Renewal Foundation, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 557)
  - Council for Urban Economic Development, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 558-560)
  - Council for Urban Economic Development, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 561)
  - Council to the Institute for Suburban Government, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 562)
  - Domestic Council, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 563)
  - Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association, 1964-1977 (Box 67, Folder 564-568)
    Press kit; Lower Manhattan fact book; publications.
  - Downtown Brooklyn Development Association, 1974-1976 (Box 67, Folder 569)
  - Economic Development Administration, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 570)
  - Economic Development Council, 1967-1977 (Box 68, Folder 571)
  - Embarcadero Center, 1968-1974 (Box 68, Folder 572-575)
    Phase I; Block 230; Westbay review and summary.
  - Embarcadero Center, 1974-1975 (Box 69, Box 576-578)
    Subphase IIA; construction financing.
  - Embarcadero Center, 1973-1975 (Box 70, Folder 579-585)
    Block 232 and Block 233; Morgan Guaranty loan; Crocker Bank loan; fire station site.
  - Embarcadero Center, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 586-588)
    Crocker Bank loan.
  - Federal National Mortgage Association (FNMA), 1975-1976 (Box 71, Folder 589-594)
    Forum II: Reports, Finance panel, transcript, clippings.
  - Fantus Study, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 595)
  - Fantus Study, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 596-601)
  - Fantus Study, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 602)
  - Farrington Project: Atlanta, Georgia, 1974-1975 (Box 73, Folder 603)
  - Flatbush Redevelopment Corporation, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 604)
  - L'Enfant Plaza Properties, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 605)
  - Maine: General, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 606)
  - Maine: Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Gardens, 1964-1976 (Box 73, Folder 607)
  - Maine: Acadia Park Exchange, 1970-1976 (Box 73, Folder 608)
  - Maine: Acadia Park Master Plan, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 609)
  - Maine: Accounts, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 610)
  - Maine: Airport Improvement, 1968-1974 (Box 73, Folder 611)
  - Maine: Bartlett Island, 1974-1976 (Box 74, Folder 612)
  - Maine: Carter's Real Estate, 1976 (Box 74, Folder 613)
  - Maine: Cottages: General, 1961-1973 (Box 74, Folder 614)
  - Maine: Cottages: Clement Rental, 1963-1973 (Box 74, Folder 615)
  - Maine: Cottages: Conies Rental, 1965-1976 (Box 74, Folder 616)
  - Maine: Cottages: Smallridge Rental, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 617)
  - Maine: Cottages: Spruces Rental, 1963; 1974 (Box 74, Folder 618)
  - Maine: Cottages: Leases, 1976 (Box 74, Folder 619)
  - Maine: Economic Development, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 620)
  - Maine: Kebo Valley Country Club, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 621)
  - Maine: Land Use Ordinance, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 622)
  - Maine: Lobsters, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 623)
  - Maine: Long Island, 1968-1974 (Box 74, Folder 624)
  - Maine: Northeast Harbor Golf Club, 1971-1974 (Box 74, Folder 625)
  - Maine: Real Estate Offerings and Sales, 1975-1976 (Box 74, Folder 626)
  - Maine: Seal Harbor Sewer Service, 1974-1976 (Box 74, Folder 627)
  - Maine: Seal Harbor Yacht Club, 1975-1976 (Box 74, Folder 628)
  - Maine: Swan's Island: Eaton Property, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 629)
  - Maine: Swan's Island: Killam Property, 1968-1973 (Box 75, Folder 630)
  - Maine: Swan's Island: Lambert Property, 1969-1974 (Box 75, Folder 631)
  - Maine: Swan's Island: McDonald Property, 1971-1973 (Box 75, Folder 632)
  - Maine: Swan's Island: Marmo Property, 1970-1974 (Box 75, Folder 633)
  - Maine: Taxes, 1975-1976 (Box 75, Folder 634)
  - Mitchell-Lama Housing Project, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 635)
  - Moreland Commission on Urban Development Corporation, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 636)
  - Mutual Housing Project: S.F. Boden, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 637)
  - Municipal Assistance Corporation, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 638)
  - New York City: General, 1971-1973 (Box 75, Folder 639)
  - New York City: General, 1975-1976 (Box 76, Folder 640)
  - New York City: Mayor, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 641)
  - New York Clearing House Association, 1976-1977 (Box 76, Folder 642)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation (NYC CPC): Annual Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 76, Folder 643)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Alternative Plans, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 644)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Charter and By-Laws, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 645)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Basic Fact Sheet and Brochure, 1975-1977 (Box 76, Folder 646)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Calendar of Events, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 647)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Candidates, 1974-1976 (Box 76, Folder 648)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 649-650)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 651)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Clippings, 1974-1976 (Box 77, Folder 652)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Crown Heights, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 653)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Documents, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 654)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Fact Sheet, 1975-1976 (Box 77, Folder 655)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: FHA Program, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 656)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Board of Directors Meetings, 1974-1976 (Box 77, Folder 657-663)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Board of Directors Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 78, Folder 664-668)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Board of Directors Minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 78, Folder 673-684)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Steering Committee Minutes, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 685)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Annual Meeting, 1976 October 14 (Box 79, Folder 686)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Mortgage Facilities Corporation, 1973-1974 (Box 79, Folder 687)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Institutional Mortgage Program, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 688)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Pittsburgh Program, 1974-1975 (Box 79, Folder 689)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Progress Report, 1974 April (Box 79, Folder 690)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Proposed Corporation, 1974 April (Box 79, Folder 691)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Washington Heights, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 692)
  - New York City Community Preservation Corporation: Reference Files, 1973-1974 (Box 79, Folder 693-695)
  - New Communities: Conference Board, 1970-1974 (Box 80, Folder 696)
  - New Communities: Boisi Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 80, Folder 697-699)
  - New Communities: Development Foundation, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 700)
  - New Communities: Lindquist Notes, 1970-1972 (Box 80, Folder 701)
  - New Communities: David Rockefeller's Senate Testimony, 1966 November 29 (Box 81, Folder 702)
  - New Communities: David Rockefeller's Interview by U.S. News and World Report, 1971 June 7 (Box 81, Folder 703)
  - New Communities: David Rockefeller's Bond Club Speech, 1973 April 15 (Box 81, Folder 704)
  - New Communities: Lindquist Statement to Senate, 1971 September 28 (Box 81, Folder 705)
  - New Communities: Housing Act, 1974 (Box 81, Folder 706)
  - New Communities: David Rockefeller's Statement to the House Banking Committee, 1971 September 29 (Box 81, Folder 707)
  - New Communities: National Growth Policy, 1969-1970 (Box 81, Folder 708)
  - New Communities: Other Proposals, 1971-1972 (Box 81, Folder 709-710)
  - New Communities: Outline of Proposal, 1970-1971 (Box 81, Folder 711)
  - New Communities: Proposed Legislation for House of Representatives, 1971-1972 (Box 81, Folder 712)
  - New Communities: Proposed Legislation for Senate, 1970-1972 (Box 82, Folder 713)
  - New Communities: Proposed Legislation Planning, 1971-1972 (Box 82, Folder 714)
  - New Communities: Real Estate Research Corporation, 1971-1974 (Box 82, Folder 715)
  - New Communities: Reference, 1970-1971 (Box 82, Folder 716)
  - New Communities: Regional Plan Association: DR Award, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 717)
  - New Communities: Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 718)
  - New Communities: Staff Candidates, 1971-1972 (Box 83, Folder 719)
  - New Communities: U.S. National Growth Policy Paper, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 720)
  - New Communities: U.S. National Development Bank, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 721)
  - New Communities: Source Material for Speeches, 1969-1972 (Box 83, Folder 722-723)
  - New York City: Rand Institute, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 724)
  - New York State Urban Development Corporation, 1974-1975 (Box 83, Folder 725)
  - New York Urban Coalition: Task Force, 1975-1976 (Box 83, Folder 726-728)
    Meeting and reports.
  - National Committee Against Discrimination Housing, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 729)
  - Housing Rental Control, 1975 (Box 84, Box 730)
  - National Association of Housing and Redevelopment Officials, 1972-1977 (Box 84, Folder 731)
  - Office Procedures, 1960-1977 (Box 84, Folder 732)
  - Producers Council, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 733)
  - Phipps Houses, 1975-1976 (Box 84, Folder 734-737)
    General correspondence; quarterly reports
  - Phipps Houses: Quarterly Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 85, Folder 738-739)
  - Ramapo Mountain, New Jersey, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 740)
  - Redlining, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 741)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1975-1977 (Box 85, Folder 742)
  - Remedco Foundation, 1973-1975 (Box 85, Folder 743)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund: Community Development, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 744)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1973-1975 (Box 85, Folder 745)
  - Rockefeller, David: Insurance (CLOSED FOLDER), 1973-1976 (Box 85, Folder 746)
    Closed Folder: Restricted material
  - Rockefeller, David: Summary Drafts by W. G. Wing, 1975 (Box 85, Folder 747)
  - Rockefeller, Eileen (CLOSED FOLDER), 1974 (Box 85, Folder 748)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance: National Growth Policy, 1972-1973 (Box 85, Folder 749)
  - Rockefeller University, 1972-1975 (Box 85, Folder 750)
  - Rose Creek Mountain Area (Arkansas), 1971 (Box 86, Folder 751)
  - St. Bart's Property, 1973-1975 (Box 86, Folder 752)
  - Staten Island, New York, 1971-1973 (Box 86, Folder 753)
  - Texfi Industries, 1972-1973 (Box 86, Folder 754)
  - Trilateral Commission Publictions, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 755)
  - University of Louisville, 1971-1972 (Box 86, Folder 756)
  - Urban Home Ownership Corporation, 1971-1977 (Box 86, Folder 757-758)
  - US-USSR Joint Committee on Housing, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 759-760)
    Russia trip; Luncheon.
  - Wilsey and Ham Inc., 1975 (Box 87, Folder 761)
  - World Trade Centers Association, 1970-1973 (Box 87, Folder 762)
  - World Trade Center, 1973-1976 (Box 87, Folder 763)
  - Wall Street Journal, 1975-1976 (Box 87, Folder 764)
  - Westbay Community Associates, 1974-1977 (Box 87, Folder 765)
  - Westchester County Housing, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 766)
  - NCOA Housing Corporation, 1971-1977 (Box 87, Folder 767)
  - Federal Programs on Housing and Rehabilitation, 1975-1976 (Box 87, Folder 768)